<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Outposts can evolve over time. Activated beacons will increase the chance of an outpost upgrading to a higher tier.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Blockades are heavily guarded stations used to control the access to deeper regions of Europa using large mechanical gates.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Settlers are always looking to expand human presence on Europa. You can help by delivering materials to Construction sites.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ You can find all kind of goods and services at Pirate Havens. They will buy and sell items at a higher price than anywhere else.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ You won't get an opportunity to buy a new submarine everywhere. Make sure you planned to upgrade before entering a new biome. Your mechanic might also have talents to help withstand the pressure of deeper regions.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ It's sometimes cheaper to visit a hospital than to waste medicine on minor wounds.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Factories will produce large amount of goods and offer a good amount of deals, but don't bother selling your surplus items there.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Factories will produce large amount of goods and offer a good amount of deals, but don't bother selling your surplus items there.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ While you can side with one faction in the conflict between Coalition and Separatists, it can be wiser to stay on good terms with everyone.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ When visiting a City, don't forget to check the mudraptor races!</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Mining outposts are looking for contractors to explore newly discovered pockets of dry caves and acquire precious minerals.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ If you are using ‖color:gui.orange‖Hungry Europans:‖end‖ (you should!), you will find a food store at Hydroponic stations.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ The ever elusive Sinking Circus is always on the move and never stays at the same location for long. It's unclear why the clowns move in such an erratic pattern.</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ You will encounter a wide variety of unfamiliar new missions. Pay attention!</loadingscreentip>
  <loadingscreentip>‖color:150,150,255‖Dynamic Europa:‖end‖ Lairs have been a thorn in the colonists' expansion plans as they prevent the development of outposts near them.</loadingscreentip>
</infotexts>